Sister, what are you doing now?
I'm busy.
Go away.
Very busy.
Ah, sister.
No...
I just said I'm busy.
Hi everyone, welcome to Super Serious Boy
. You can see the building behind me
and the Korean text on it.
Today's episode is
안녕하세요.
In this episode, we're going to talk about electronic locks.
So why did we come to Korea to film this?
Because, do you know that
the reason electronic locks have developed on a large scale worldwide
is
because of Korea?
This factory is basically the master of electronic locks.
Basically, from the time
you saw
oppas in Korean dramas more than 40 years ago, pressing the electronic lock so coolly
and being able to enter
in style, to the present day,
we can use fingerprints
, visual recognition
, or palm vein
recognition
. This factory has made a great contribution to all of this.
You'll find that it's the Korean factory behind me. The sheer number of Taiwanese women
who have built up the entire electronic lock industry
is astonishing.
So, on this day,
which happens to be zero degrees Celsius
, we made a special trip to South Korea
to film an electronic lock company.
Besides electronic locks, this episode
will also discuss a way to make money. According to statistics,
the penetration rate of electronic locks
in South Korea
is around 98%,
while in Taiwan it
's less than 30%
. That means over 70% of the money-making opportunities
lie in electronic locks.
But have you ever wondered
why, even though electronic locks are so widespread in South Korea
, many Taiwanese people still don't install them
, or don't want to replace them?
They often lose their keys , frequently need to call a locksmith
, or often can't open their doors.
It turns out that many people
have a very negative impression
of electronic locks;
Taiwanese people don't like installing them.
There are four main reasons why electronic locks
are so prone to failure. First, they are expensive.
Second, they often run out of power , requiring
battery replacements
or becoming unusable.
Third,
many people find that electronic locks break down easily after installation.
Fourth, and most importantly,
besides the high price of locks
, Taiwan has a wide variety of door sizes,
which contributes to
the high cost of replacing electronic locks.
However, you can
find the answers to these questions
by watching this episode . Why did early electronic locks break down so easily?
Because the evolution of electronic locks
to the present day is roughly 40 years
old. Over 40 years ago, they were basically operated by entering passwords
or using cards.
Think about it:
40 years ago, many things didn't
exist. There was no national
health insurance, no GPS... PS
didn't have smartphones
40 years ago, nor did it have democracy.
So, in just 40 years,
you can see how many new things
and technologies have developed
. Its technology has evolved step by step.
Although many people mistakenly believe that
many components are imported from mainland China,
or that visual recognition is
synonymous with facial recognition and
Chinese devices,
have you ever wondered
why many people don't use facial recognition?
Because facial recognition raises personal data concerns.
And why has facial recognition technology developed so well in China?
Because
the Party needs it,
the Party needs your face.
So, regardless,
let's go into the factory and see
how this electronic lock works. This is how they did it.
The largest electronic lock factory in South Korea,
a factory comprised of a group of South Korean middle-aged women
, can change the entire South Korean electronic lock market. Just
how big and amazing is this production line?
It can produce more than 3,000 electronic locks a day! That
's how big it is,
unbelievable!
How amazing are these South Korean middle
-aged women? One out of every two electronic locks in South Korea
is made by them.
If you
've ever wanted to replace your electronic lock
, or if you find electronic locks convenient
but don't understand their structure,
then in this episode, I will try my best
to explain the principles of electronic locks to the general public
in a way that you can understand,
and how to choose an electronic lock.
First, stand in
the center of me.
Imagine me as... One door
after another,
electronic locks will definitely have front-opening and back-opening
options.
When choosing an electronic lock,
you don't need to listen to a lot of
jargon about
how great it is or what functions it has.
You can explain it into three main categories:
how to open, how to pull,
and how to lock. What does "how to open" mean
? It refers to how
an electronic lock opens.
Nowadays, there are many functions:
fingerprint unlocking,
Wi-Fi unlocking
, password unlocking
, card unlocking , and
recently popular
visual recognition like facial
and palm vein recognition.
The second option is how to pull.
Whether you're opening or closing,
you need to pull the door.
There are several
ways to pull
: one is like a traditional horn lock,
and another... So ,
the third type is the 90-degree rotating handle,
and
the second type is
the pull-pull type.
How do you pull it?
The third type is how to lock it.
Actually, the third type is the most important of all.
That's why we went to a factory in Korea to film
this – the most important thing is how to lock it.
If
you
're not a locksmith,
you usually won't see this.
The most important
part of an electronic lock is the lock cylinder
. The lock cylinder's structure
is actually very simple.
We can use a 3D diagram to show you.
The lock cylinder
is installed on your door panel.
When the door panel
is opened or closed,
this thing
touches your door, and
it senses the door... Once it's closed,
it will automatically lock.
Or, when
you're opening it, the latch—
this latch
, this bean curd—
is on your tongue.
How smoothly
it opens and closes
depends entirely on
the
quality of the basic hardware and industrial processing
.
So why do I say the third point, how to lock,
is the most important? Because
locking a door,
you know, a door lock is a door.
If a door can't be locked,
what's the
point of having a door
?
So, does that make sense
Now, if I have Wi-Fi,
visual recognition,
fingerprint, and palm vein recognition
, I can pull and push the door like a mansion door,
automatically locking after someone leaves.
The door won't lock
in two seconds
, so many people use exaggerated
features like "what functions it has" to
describe it . But the most important thing is that it's
like a car with a beautiful
interior , lots
of trim panels, and
built-in navigation—
what's the use
if the engine breaks down?
So, I think
many people want to buy an electronic lock
, but the first thing you should care about is
where the lock cylinder is made.
That's
the key
. Now that you have these three basic concepts—
how to open
, how to pull, and how to lock—
we can look at
how an electronic lock is installed
. First, what kind of components do you need to install
? Let's
go to
the small parts area at the very beginning
of the factory . First, we need to install the door handle. The door
handle looks like this.
If you want to add a function
, you need to add a small component,
like a
fingerprint sensor
. If you want to add a fingerprint sensor
to your door handle,
the first thing is to make an opening
during injection molding.
Then, you need to install the
fingerprint
electronic component.
This way, when you push the door handle,
your fingerprint can be pressed.
So, it's back to
the present day... Adding one more part
means one more expense,
and adding one more part means one more electricity consumption.
So let's start
assembling our door handle.
Well...
speaking of which...
adding one more part
means one more electricity consumption.
Let's install our handle.
Huh?
You didn't get it?
I didn't get it?
Adding one more part means one more electricity consumption,
a little bit
more electricity,
and then it's all about the handle.
The handle is
too subtle, isn't it?
Let's install the handle.
In a short moment,
the Korean aunties have already formed their own production line
. In fact, every single one of them,
every single one of them, they all
know how to do it . So they're like
a guerrilla force now
. When they find something stuck at the back,
they run to the front. When they find something stuck at the front, they start locking it.
Now they start automatically gluing it.
From
beginning to end,
no foreman or supervisor has come to talk to them.
They haven't said a word. They've
all been aligning themselves with their bodies.
From the moment they started assembling until now,
they haven't said a word.
So now, you see in front of me,
a whole row of very cute
array-style production lines has appeared
at this station. There's a small detail
you can see. Look at our second auntie.
In front of her, where she's tightening the screws, there's a machine .
That machine is called
KILEWS. KILEWS
is an automatic screw feeder.
Its internal structure is simple and interesting.
Previously, when tightening screws,
you'd pick up a screw,
then use a screwdriver or drill
to tighten it
. So, for each part,
you had to pick up a screw from a bunch, align
the Phillips head
with the screwdriver, and then tighten
it – very cumbersome.
But with KILEWS, it 's
different.
When you open it, there's a scoop inside.
It scoops up the screw, and
due to
gravity, it falls to the middle,
like a row of
screws forming a bridge.
There's a broom-like mechanism that keeps
sweeping . The principle is that
if the screw threads
aren't on the bottom,
it will be swept away, and
the
screws on the bottom
will be inserted into the feeder.
Finally, it's fed out from the outlet at the front.
So, it's very convenient when you pick up
a screwdriver ; you can
simply insert
your hand, and the screwdriver tip will be aligned with the screw.
Isn't that convenient?
You know, this technology has been around for a long time
, but many factories in Taiwan
still don't buy it. It
's very useful,
KILEWS.
Our channel has filmed many factories in recent years, and you've probably
seen many production lines
and assembly plants.
How
can we understand
a company
that can produce such high output and production lines
with a small workforce ?
Because, as you know, in South Korea
, regardless of whether it's an S-brand
or L-brand,
all of them are made in this factory.
They are basically the
original Godzilla
of electronic locks
, the earliest founders
. Actually, as people in industrial manufacturing and design, we
have a few concepts that
I think can be shared with many bosses or factories
in Taiwan for reference
. For example, the first is that this
may seem like nothing
, just a casting.
Everyone can make castings
, but you know,
the base of
many electronic locks, its casting
, is actually common.
And this casting
can be used in many
different brands and models of electronic locks,
somewhat like a car chassis.
It has become one of the most commonly used car chassis in the world,
and many others... Different brands
can all be placed on this chassis
to form a new car and
a new brand.
This is a very unique approach they take.
Secondly,
the electronic locks all look very similar
. Actually,
there's another reason why
they look so similar: the trim
panels. If
I were to steal a
Korean lady's trim panel, would she be angry?
When you look at it from the side, you might think, "
Why do some big Korean brands
or Japanese manufacturers
all look a bit the same?
" The second reason is that
the trim
panels may use different colors,
different injection molded parts
, or different styles
, such as leather
, wood grain
, or marble patterns.
But
they all use common components.
So, their supply chain can,
for example, use the same castings and
injection molded parts
. They can serve 30 or
50 brands at once
, reducing costs
and making their supply chain very efficient.
And in this location,
all the materials,
castings,
and electronic components
can be delivered
within a two-hour drive .
Their factory doesn't need to be very large.
Because it's readily available—
I order as much as I need today,
and it
's delivered within two hours
—or if there's a problem with the materials,
its suppliers
can immediately help resolve the issue.
Therefore,
the supply chain is crucial.
If an industry can thrive
, like in Korean dramas where you
first see electronic locks that make you think, "
Wow, these electronic locks
are so cool !"—
and then the industry
and its supply chain
provide excellent service,
you can build a very long-lasting
business.
From this concept,
you can see why it uses half plastic
and half metal
components . If you use all metal,
the door will still have weight.
When the torque is high, and
you're hanging something heavy nearby,
the half-metal,
half-plastic design
allows for more development.
Also, it's inevitable
that every household
will encounter conflicts, like
doors being slammed
or kicked when people are unhappy.
Metal components also increase the sturdiness
compared to the traditional
all-plastic design.
Now that you have this concept,
you can see why it has gained
favor with many major brands,
including many Taiwanese manufacturers
like
3E. Xiaodao Electronic Locks
are all made here.
Do you know why? Do you know
why
you can't see it? It
's right here.
You know, after I got to know this factory
in Korea,
I found that many Taiwanese manufacturers are dishonest.
You know, this brand
has factories in Vietnam
, China
, and all over the world.
Being able to use Korean factories is obviously impressive
, like their
high-end manufacturing.
So some of the better and
more expensive products
are actually made in Korean factories
. I found
that some Taiwanese manufacturers
lied to me, saying that everything was made in Taiwan.
Is it better to be made in Taiwan or Korea?
No,
I don't care which is better or worse.
They're dishonest, lying to you
and me.
I think they might just take the parts to Taiwan, assemble
them in Taiwan, and then say it's made in Taiwan.
They 're not
being honest.
But you know,
3E... When Xiaodao
was raising funds
, everyone in the lock industry thought
it was incredibly impressive
because the fundraising was extremely successful
. They included the installation of
the brand's system,
which is actually called "Da Nei Gao Shou" (Great Master of the
Interior ). Don't think the name sounds tacky;
let me tell you, Da Nei Gao Shou is very powerful.
I actually know some insider gossip about them,
which I'll share in the member videos.
So, if you want to support our channel,
you can join our membership for 60 yuan. You
'll often get
special discounts
and access to many previously unseen videos,
all of which we'll include in the member videos. You
can also support our travel expenses.
If you haven't seen the member videos,
just remember one thing:
the owner of Da Nei Gao Shou, Boss
Tu,
claims
there's no lock he can't open and
no lock he can't install.
He works 365 days a year without rest,
and many famous and powerful figures in Taiwan find his locks
very difficult to open. He unlocks all the car door locks,
so you know
, the hardest lock to open isn't actually a door lock
or a vault lock,
but
a car door lock.
The simplest way is to break the car window
, but
that's still unlocking.
Let
's say it's a big boss like
Kenneth Yen.
He even unlocked
the lock on Kenneth Yen's first Tesla
, and without damaging the car.
Then there are sports cars and supercars.
For example, if you're shipping something overseas
, the shipping time is very long.
My friend has a Ferrari, and he unlocked it for him.
Otherwise, would you break the glass of a Ferrari,
or would you dare to pry it open
and use a metal piece to scratch
the paint?
If the paint is scratched,
the car is ruined .
So, unlocking car door locks is the hardest thing.
Frankly,
look at Taiwan; there's still a 70-80%
untapped market.
If you want to find a locksmith,
I suggest you go to... If you ask him
to teach you lock picking,
he 's incredibly skilled.
I think someone who truly understands lock picking
is even more capable
of installing and making locks
because he understands the structural principles
. Basically,
any electronic lock made in this factory
can be installed in Taiwan.
Even the oldest door in your house,
like your bathroom plastic door,
can be installed. It can fit both
real and fake
locks. Lock installation
is a technical skill.
As I mentioned, Taiwan
doesn't have
its own standards,
so each lock requires multiple installers .
You need to know how to use a grinder and
a cutting machine. After grinding,
you need to repair it
, much like doing handicrafts.
You need to be able to install different electronic locks on
different brands of
doors.
This is one
reason
why lock installation in Taiwan
is more expensive than in Korea
. In Korea, the standards
are all the same,
so many Korean locks... If people
can install door locks themselves,
can I hire
a Korean "Oppa" to install
my door locks
in Korea? Yes , but
it's about the same price in Taiwan dollars
,
around 1000+ NTD. It's simple; it's just disassembly, locking, and installation. Taiwanese locksmiths are more expensive because they need to modify, cut, or repair the door. If they damage the door, you have to pay compensation, which is a risk. If your door is damaged by construction companies like
Shuangxiangyuan
,
Longbao
or
Jingrui,
it
's
bad
luck
; I might have to pay tens of thousands in compensation for a simple lock installation. And do you know that the most important home appliance in Taiwan is the electronic lock? If your
light
bulb
is
broken
,
you
can
wait
two
weeks
to fix it; if your
faucet is broken,
you can replace the bathroom faucet.
But if your front door lock is broken,
how are you going to get in
? Your whole family has to wait outside until the locksmith arrives.
So I know many people have the urge to replace their locks with electronic ones
, but
please don't be greedy and buy cheap, low-quality stuff
. Just one lock will make you
unhappy for a whole month.
My dad was locked out once and
scolded me for three months
straight
. You know,
our door lock
is actually made by a Korean factory.
I think these Korean aunties
work hard
to protect our family's safety,
so I think
we should express
our respect and love for them
. Sister
- Sister, you're so pretty. - Go away.
Sister, you're so pretty.
Oh dear, I told you I was busy.
I told you to go away.
You're so pretty, sister.
I love you.
Hurry up and go away.
I love you, sister.
Hey~ (disgusted voice)
I 'm busy.
Sister.
You're so pretty.
I love you.
Oh dear, why are you like this?
You 're so pretty, sister.
She's an old hand,
didn't succeed
. Sister.
Is that right?
You're pretty.
What should I say...
I love you, sister.
No, although I find it annoying.
But because he's so handsome, I can't bring myself to curse him.
Look, it's slowly accumulating here,
and lunchtime is almost here.
Look, it's
12:30 now. It stopped as
soon as
it hit 30, and then they left
for lunch.
I thought they'd
eat like that Korean Minister Kim,
and then rush off
. The older women
are
quite reserved
. What do Korean older women eat?
I followed them
to a small eatery. Hey,
a Korean small eatery
... this reminds me of the one I ate when I was little...
Han Il-gwan, do you remember it?
Han Il-gwan Korean BBQ
... They need
soup in this
... Oh, they need soup in this...
Sorry,
I didn't know
... I don't know ...
I'm..." "Hai" What?
This is Korea.
This is how Taiwanese people put things.
The proper way to put things in Korea is like this.
And do you
know how much a whole plate like this
costs?
6500 Korean won,
150 NT dollars. It's all-you-can-eat
, meaning if you get hungry in the middle,
it's a gift from the Korean lady. Oh,
it's a gift from the Korean lady
. Thank you,
I'm so happy.
(Ten minutes later)
They eat super fast, so rushed!
We've only put our food down for the fifth bite.
Then everyone else has finished eating.
It's so nice to have a cafeteria here.
Everyone finished eating in 15 minutes.
The auntie is so happy.
We're full now.
The Korean lady said she would
take us to see their headquarters.
There's a showroom,
so we walked there.
It's a Korean electronic lock company.
Since you've come to the factory,
you'll inevitably have to come to their headquarters.
Since we've come to the birthplace of electronic locks, let's have
a display to show you
the various types
and features of electronic locks.
First, look here.
Cut across from this line in the middle
and look
this way. This is actually all Korean domestic sales.
So you see
the English name SOLITY written here
. It's actually the Korean domestic sales brand
, which is the
Korean pronunciation of
this company.
SOLITY
. But everyone will surely think of
the traditional
locks we used to make ,
especially those large locks for luxury homes, right?
They had a row of
buttons on top, which
was very complicated . But if you look at this,
you'll see that in South Korea,
the birthplace of electronic lock masters
, their locks are so simple.
The bolt is
just a small section like this.
Do you know what the biggest difference is?
Of course, it can be traced back to the mechanical principle and structure. Because it's
more energy-efficient and less labor-intensive
to move smaller things.
And the biggest reason is that
there are fewer people breaking into homes now. Furthermore
, thieves these days
usually lack skills;
they can only pick
doors you've forgotten to lock,
or climb in through windows.
The kind of skill
you need to unlock slowly
is what truly matters. Those skilled
locksmiths have all become
thieves; why bother? Things
have become more about
protecting honest people from dishonest ones.
People don't keep
much gold or cash
at home anymore.
Those who want to steal large sums of money
are now resorting to fraud.
The worst kind of
fraudsters have
no skills or
expertise , so
learning lock picking would be better
. Therefore, prisons should teach people lock picking
instead of fraud; they should teach them to steal.
We can lie to them and say... You can steal more things,
and then I'll teach you how to
pick locks. After learning how to pick locks, you'll find
that you can make more money
by picking locks for people who have forgotten their keys
at night. You
'll also see the police and not be afraid. It's
a legitimate business
. When you're outside,
you'll help people open doors,
but they
still can't open your electronic lock.
This is for export.
In Japan,
they have some horizontal bar locks,
and this one is exported to the US.
But do you know why American locks are
sold? People might think that
the US has a worse security situation
, but why do American locks only use one lock?
Because installing more won't
help. People will still
break it. They'll break it.
They'll dismantle the whole door.
But you'll see
that the structure and the way the American lock is drilled
are actually very simple.
In the US,
the wages
are extremely high. If you go there, just for site inspection
and nothing else,
you might spend 5,000 or 6,000 NT dollars.
So almost everyone there does their own installation
. In Korea
, many people can also do
it themselves.
So you see, in Korea,
everyone's specifications are actually the same.
There's the Korean standard,
the Japanese
standard, and
the American standard.
Of course, there's also an American standard.
Taiwan is the most special.
Taiwan doesn't have a Taiwanese standard.
Taiwan's doors have
Japanese, Korean, American, and European/American standards.
So many people
are worried about whether
electronic locks can be installed in their homes.
There's a simple way to check
: just look at the thickness
of the core. If it's
thin, it's generally fine.
In Taiwan, there are old doors (30-40 years old)
and old brass doors
that are very thin
, or even thick doors in luxury homes
. The locks that are easy to install are those that can fit
both thin and thick doors
. That's why we filmed this company
– because they can install locks
of almost all kinds of odd and unusual sizes in Taiwan.
Otherwise,
it's
useless if
the lock can't be installed,
but it's
too difficult to install it yourself. If you can
install it yourself, why not?
I can do it
! It's your problem
that you can't install it.
Actually,
electronic locks are divided into several types.
The first type
is the kind you used to see in Korean dramas,
which is a button type.
It's similar to a traditional home telephone.
This type is
more intuitive for
the elderly and children . You might prefer touch control
, which uses a combination lock.
Another type
is card-based,
like the
MRT card, EasyCard, or
RFID.
You just use the card
and beep to set it up.
The third type
is fingerprint.
You press your
fingerprint in and it identifies it.
It says "
Unregistered fingerprint."
I'll listen again.
Unregistered fingerprint.
Actually, there's a problem with fingerprints.
For example, you see...
Before I came to Korea, if
you were ever hurt or damaged
at work, you
might feel very embarrassed and suddenly find yourself unable to get into your own home.
I suggest
you try using different fingers
and setting
different angles for each finger,
just in case you can't get in.
Another type is the
facial recognition system
, where you scan your face to enter.
Some also have buttons
or passwords,
and some use RFID
, which is card-based.
But sometimes it has evolved into a system
where facial recognition scans your face to see
if you can get in.
Sometimes twins have
even been found to be able to enter each other's homes.
There was also an experiment online that
... If you print a photo of a person
and place it on the screen
, and the door opens,
it's fake.
That's
impossible; the photo
is fake . Or, the person might be drunk,
and a friend might carry them to their doorstep
and lift their face like that.
That's possible
, of course
. So basically, as long as the face is the person's,
regardless of whether they're drunk
, sober
, or unconscious
, as long as you can grab the person's head
and scan the camera,
it can generally open the door.
But you might be thinking, what
if I scan my face
, 3D print my head
, or use silicone molding
to create a
mask of myself?
That's basically impossible
because the camera
doesn't scan flat. The surface
is actually three-dimensional, corresponding to the position,
and there's infrared light to
scan your blood,
whether your pupils are blinking
, or your
breathing dynamics.
It scans a lot of things.
But before this,
we filmed several different lock
videos or posts
, and everyone had the same question:
What if I'm in Taiwan
and suddenly go abroad for a long time
and come back to Taiwan with an electronic lock
that runs out of power?
It's simple, just
go to a convenience store to buy batteries.
There aren't many
convenience stores in Taiwan; at most
, you go to a convenience store
and buy an AA battery
. We'll
say
AA battery
, or even just a
5 -size battery
. Which one is it?
Think carefully before answering.
For example ,
if this has two 'A's,
it's called a '3' battery in Taiwan. In
South Korea and mainland China, it's called a '5' battery.
The smaller one
is called a '4' battery.
But in South Korea and mainland China,
they call a '7' battery (three 'A's).
It's complicated
, and you don't need to know.
If you need to replace the battery,
it's in the back
of the indoor unit.
But if
I 'm outside
and need emergency power,
the product has two
battery terminals
that can supply 9V batteries.
You need to plug the battery into these
terminals, and the keypad light will illuminate.
I think another significant
difference that people encounter is
that now everyone... I really like using lithium batteries
because rechargeable batteries
seem more environmentally friendly and useful.
However,
why aren't lithium batteries used
in South Korea?
(Chinese is fine, thank you.
) While lithium batteries have a significant advantage
—
high charging capacity
and the ability to support various
current technologies
—
the safety regulations for lithium batteries in South Korea
are quite limited.
Recent news reports have highlighted
the potential
for explosions caused by
lithium batteries.
For everyday use,
dry cell batteries are generally considered safer
than lithium batteries. Therefore, dry cell batteries are currently used in
the production and research of electronic door locks in South Korea.
Among the R&D teams
in South Korea that develop locks
powered by
dry
cell
batteries , only our company
can currently
do this. (Your Chinese is very good,
thank you.
Please explain again in Korean.
There's a complete Korean introduction at the end; remember to watch until the end
. If you don't understand,
thank you
.) In other words, the most difficult thing is
having two battery storage capacities simultaneously
—
one with a large energy
output and the other with a small energy output
. However, if you use a small amount of
battery power for multiple unlocking methods,
the energy consumption will increase.
They are so impressive that they can use a very small amount of battery power.
Then we can achieve many system
challenges here.
Usually, we
can use eight batteries
for 10 to 12 months.
What do we mean by eight batteries?
Eight batteries,
eight cells.
I've been thinking about something
. You guys have some
door opening methods, right?
In Korea, it's all pulled outwards.
Have you ever thought about
installing a
hand-cranked generator inside
? So when the power is out,
I can just pull it ten times
and it will open.
Okay? I
haven't
proposed this to your boss yet , but this might be
related to its fixed structure.
Plus,
because our structures are
mostly shared,
the entire
series might need to be modified.
So the boss hasn't done it. The French
developed a new structure
for my new concept
, otherwise you
wouldn't need to do it yourself .
It's faster to buy 9V batteries than to redevelop this.
But I'll say it first
: see which country
doesn't follow my idea of
​​hand-operated power generation.
So you see, if you want to use very low power,
and at the same time you need to use a screen camera
to identify whether it's alive,
whether it's a face
, and also look at fingerprints
, and at the same time want to enter a password
, everyone will be afraid
and have privacy issues.
Will my face be copied?
Will it be uploaded to another cloud?
So at this time,
everyone thought of a very new thing,
do you know what it is?
Offline
palm vein
back to the Korean aunt's production line
palm vein model. What does the
palm vein module look like? You can think of it
as roughly the same as the fingerprint module
we talked about this morning.
You install this module,
and
it can detect the palm veins in your palm.
You should know that palm veins don't require touching, right?
You just need to touch it. Yes
, just touch it.
Actually, the palm vein module detects
the blood vessels inside your veins.
It uses a near-infrared principle
and simultaneously checks
whether your blood is flowing and
whether you are a living person.
In the past, people said that with fingerprint locks,
you could just cut off someone's finger
and use it for fingerprint recognition.
Palm veins couldn't detect fingerprints
. If blood flow on the face
cannot be detected,
then you can't open the door.
So why has palm vein recognition
become so popular
in recent years ? It stems from the pandemic;
doorknobs
were being disinfected extensively.
Palm vein
recognition allows for contactless opening. But how do you open the door?
You can push with your elbow
, you can squeeze with your body,
you can unlock it first, and then
push the door open.
I personally think that
palm vein recognition will be the future trend.
Why? Because
if you have young children at home
, if you use image recognition,
the child might
be jumping around
, making it difficult
for the camera to capture the child's face.
It's impossible for a vice president to do this.
If you use the palm vein method
on a two- or three-year-old child
, they might be
short enough to
reach the palm vein
by waving their hand. If the child
can walk independently
and doesn't need adult supervision,
they
can usually reach the palm vein by raising
their hand – about the height of the handle.
However, if
a child's hands are dirty
or peeling
, or if an elderly person's
skin is worn down,
fingerprint
recognition might not work for
unregistered fingerprints.
Palm vein
recognition, on the other hand, detects
the living blood vessels in the palm.
That's why many bank ATMs
use finger vein recognition – it
's based on the same principle.
And I've heard that palm vein recognition is
... If you looked like this when
you were a child, you'll probably look like this when you grow up.
It's possible that the vice president,
like when he was a child , had his palm veins programmed into the lock of my house.
He could still open the door
when he was 20,
and he could still go home
when he was 60.
Your palm
is the bloodline of our family.
As long as your palm is still there,
you can always enter our
family's door—it's our bloodline.
However, I have a question:
if I quickly
cut off that hand
and then immediately press on the palm vein
, can it open?
No, not to that extent.
Because it operates by directly connecting to the biological signals of a living organism.
If the palm is severed, the biological signals will disappear
, and the nerves will immediately die.
So it's possible to... Since it's impossible to identify
, if I use a tourniquet to bind his
hand before cutting it off
, and then bind this side as well,
and then quickly
cut it off like a Japanese samurai,
and immediately check
if there's still blood inside, will that work?
Unless it's a very fast
cut and the sensor detects it immediately
, it's ineffective.
Have you tried
this? Will the company try it in the future?
As for testing, there's currently no other way to get
results. Next time we come to the lab,
none of the lab staff will have their hands.
If it's based on fingerprints,
is there any way to
cut off a person's finger and then use their fingerprints to press them?
As far as I know, fingerprints
also work through biometrics,
unless you cut off the finger... Take it to the sensor immediately,
otherwise, as far as I know, it's currently impossible to identify.
Another question:
there's a rumor circulating
that there's an extreme method to unlock
electronic locks—
using high-voltage electricity to touch it can open it.
Technically,
is this really feasible?
We conduct thorough testing and verification
during the manufacturing of electronic locks.
We also have an internal laboratory
where we conduct comprehensive ESD (electrostatic discharge) tests
to confirm whether the door will open or not
before manufacturing the product.
So you don't need to worry about this.
Theoretically, it's possible
, but in reality,
you can't buy such high-voltage
electricity
outside. Finally,
why do Korean men like
National Geographic Channel clothes and slippers
—the most basic and inexpensive ones?
It has a great price-performance ratio
because many people wear its jackets on the street.
We also wear its jackets.
It 's a brand
that many people wear
regularly.
So, you see, in the next step,
the door lock is
gradually being completed.
Now look,
this is the palm vein
on the outside.
Occasionally,
you can use a fingerprint. If you need a password
, you can use a card.
I can put my fingerprint inside,
and then it will be sold to Taiwan.
This will have my fingerprint on it.
No, no,
that's not professional ethics
, that won't do.
Then,
look at this side. This side doesn't have a lock,
and this side doesn't have an unlocking method.
So, if you are a locksmith today,
you will get three things,
three treasures.
One is the inside,
one is the outside,
and the third is the lock box.
As long as you can connect
these three treasures,
you can make money.
Now, if you have a certain understanding
of electronic locks
and a concept of its component structure, then
where do
the 3,000 electronic locks
that our line
can produce a day go?
To Taiwan. 3E T9 Made in A Korean
-made electronic lock
is about to be shipped to Taiwan.
So, in this episode, did everyone
gain a better understanding of electronic locks
? If you're looking for an electronic lock
that only requires a yearly battery change
, can be remotely controlled,
and features palm vein recognition
, regardless of your door type
or age,
and you want to take this opportunity to upgrade,
you can contact the Korean lady
below.
This connects you to a
highly skilled team
in Taiwan who can install
high-tech electronic locks
for you for under NT$20,000.
Of course, if you're a long-time member of our channel,
you'll get an
even lower discount.
That concludes this episode
's special on the electronic lock industry, spearheaded by Korean ladies.
For those looking to install electronic locks
and earn money,
Taiwan still has a 70% untapped market –
no one installs electronic locks.
So, take this opportunity
to learn how to install them.
Hopefully, this will be helpful for your future.
This is this week's "Super Serious Youth,"
see you next week!
Bye!
Thank you.
Today we visited
another staff restaurant – a
Korean staff restaurant.
Perhaps it's
like a Taiwanese buffet –
you never know how much it will ultimately cost .
Behind them, they were cooking instant noodles. Hey,
behind them was their own pot for cooking instant noodles.
Then they looked on with a shocked expression,
wondering if
this guy was some
Taiwanese celebrity.
You know, at Taiwanese buffets, you just pick up food
and don't even know how much you've spent.
Then the
Taiwanese lady will use her mood
to calculate
your bill randomly.
There were vegetables.
Vegetables are precious in Korea
because they're mostly kimchi;
you rarely get stir-fried vegetables.
But it's still kimchi;
every meal has some kimchi
salad.
Now I know why
in that Korean drama with Kim Jong-un,
there was nothing left at the end—because
the staff cafeteria was all-you-can-eat! The
bean sprout soup
from the Korean staff meal
looks delicious!
We really travel all over the world
eating at different staff restaurants.
Does Korea have a Korean way of starting a meal?
I'm going to eat!
I'm going to eat! All
the functions of our company's electronic door locks
are operated using alkaline batteries.
Because currently,
many multi-functional door locks on the market
, especially those produced and exported from China,
use lithium
-ion batteries. Lithium-ion batteries pose a fire risk
, so using alkaline batteries
is safer and more convenient
. Moreover, technically,
our company can achieve low voltage and low current functions
by using alkaline batteries,
which is our company's biggest advantage.